Guide to the Sarah Buckingham Wilmot Nettleton Buckingham Letters
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Letters
1856-1869
WA MSS S-20
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
0.5
(1 box)
Letters between Sarah Buckingham and family and friends, between other family members, and between family and friends. Among the letters from Clark Nettleton to his sister Mrs. Goodsell is a letterhead of a 1858 view of Saint Paul, Minnesota.
Buckingham, Sarah Buckingham Wilmot Nettleton, 1803-
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Unspecified, please consult the appropriate curator.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Letters between Sarah Buckingham and family and friends, and between other family members and friends. Among the letters from Clark Nettleton to his sister Mrs. Goodsell is an 1858 view of Saint Paul, Minnesota on letterhead.
Families -- New England; Saint Paul (Minn.) -- Pictorial works; Buckingham, Sarah Buckingham Wilmot Nettleton, 1803-; Nettleton, Clark; Nettleton, Elliott W., d. 1865; Nettleton, George Wilmot
- Box and Folder List
  - Baldwin, Catherine Mills
    - AL to Clark Nettleton. Milford, Conn., 1863 Oct 4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Buckingham, Sarah Buckingham (Wilmot) Nettleton
    - Draft of AL to "Respected Friend". N.p. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ALS to "Dear Elizabeth". West Haven, Conn., n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 2 ALS to her daughter "Abby". N.p., n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 19 ALS to her son Clark Nettleton. Milford & New Haven, Conn., 1857-1865 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Nettleton, Clark
    - 17 ALS to his mother, Sarah Buckingham. V.p., 1858-1869 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 2 ALS to his brother Elliott W. Nettleton. Washington Ter. & Centerville, Idaho., 1860, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Scope and Contents
      1860 Dec 20, 1863 Dec 20.
    - 3 ALS to his sister, Mrs. Goodsell. St. Paul & Walla Walla, Washington Terrace., 1858-1860 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      1858 Aug, 1860 Sep 1, 1860 Dec 4.
  - Nettleton, Elliott W.
    - ALS to "Dear Friend". Capsville, Ga., [1864] May 20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - ALS to John Newton Buckingham. Harleyville, S.C., 1865 Jan 24 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 21 ALS to his mother Mrs. Sarah Buckingham. V.p., 1856-1864 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - AL to Clark Nettleton. Stevenson, Ala., 1863 Nov 4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Incomplete.
    - 3 ALS to George Nettleton. V.p., 1862, 1867, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
      1862 Sep 18, 1867 & undated.
    - ALS to Edward Nettleton. Littleton, Md. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Nettleton, Ephraim
    - ALS to "Brother Samuel". Tarragona, Spain., 1858 Sep 30 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Nettleton, George
    - ALS to his mother, Mrs. Sarah Buckingham. Middlebury [Mass?]., 1862 Aug 16 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Peck, Margaret
    - ALS to Clark Nettleton. Milford, Conn., 1861 Aug 4 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Letters. (Box 1, Folder 9)